zuzutop.com 2019-06-07

# Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

We Understand Your Concerns About Protecting Personal Information. Thank you for visiting Zuzutop.com!

This Site is operated by Zuzutop. Your access to and use of this Site is subject to the following Privacy Policy (“Policy”) and all applicable laws.

Zuzutop.com fully understands the need to protect your personal information while online and has developed this policy as a means to provide you with the utmost privacy possible. This Privacy Policy describes our practices regarding the collection and use of information throughout our website, located at Zuzutop.com (“Site”). By using the Site, you agree to the limited collection and use of information as outlined in this Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use the Site.

We understand your concerns about privacy and we want to assure you that Zuzutop.com takes privacy matters seriously. Therefore, we are providing this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy, click on the “Contact Us” tab and send us your questions.

Important: by submitting information manually or in electronic form to us and/or by using our Site, you give your consent that all information that you submit may be processed byZuzutop.com in the manner and for the purposes described below. Do not send Zuzutop.com any confidential or proprietary information other than as necessary to process your order. We may from time to time update this Policy to reflect changing technology and other factors. We will notify you of changes to the Policy by posting the updated Policy on this page.

## Zuzutop Collects Basic Information During Your Visits To Our Site We collect non-personal information.

This is general information that cannot be traced to individuals and contains no personalized data, think of it as a simple census form. When visitors come to our Site, we collect and aggregate information indicating, among other things, which pages of the Site were visited, the order in which they were visited and which links on the site were clicked by visitors. Collecting such information involves logging the IP addresses, operating system and browser software used by each visitor to the Site. Although such information is not personally identifiable, it may be possible to determine from an IP address a visitor’s Internet Service Provider and the general geographic location of the visitor’s point of connectivity. We attempt to use this information to provide you the user with a more efficient shopping experience.

We use non-invasive “cookies” and other tracking technologies to collect non-personally identifiable information. Our non-invasive cookies simply make it possible for us to recognize your browser once you visit our Site. By doing this, we can personalize your return visits and save you time. Your browser must be set to accept cookies in order for you to enjoy the benefits. If you are uncomfortable with the cookies on your computer, you can always remove them by accessing the options menu of your browser.

Additionally, we collect personal information as needed to provide you with maximum service and to process any order you might initiate. Our Site uses an order forms and registration forms in order for you to request information and products from us. These forms require that you provide us with personally identifiable information, such as your name, email address, mailing address, telephone number.

We cannot and do not assume any responsibility for any actions or omissions of third parties, including the manner in which they use information received from Zuzutop.com.

## Different Types of Gathered Information

Zuzutop.com uses non-personal information, such as your IP address and the pages that you visit on our Site, to help administer our Site and improve Site-related products and features. Your IP address and other non-personally identifiable information also may be used to gather demographic information and to recognize customer traffic patterns and Site usage trends. This information aids us in merchandising and in developing the design and layout of the Site.

Zuzutop.com uses personal information collected from you to complete transactions initiated by you, particularly the sale and delivery of products. Your personally identifiable information is also used to get in touch with you when necessary regarding questions about any order you might place. We may also use personally identifiable information to contact you to make sure you are satisfied with our products. Your decision to participate in any survey is completely voluntary. Further, we may use personally identifiable information to conduct in-depth marketing research regarding our customers.

Financial information including credit card numbers, credit card expiration dates, billing address, etc… is used solely to bill you for products and services and we make every effort to keep your information secure from theft or fraud. We use industry standard encryption technologies, and all credit card / bank information submitted on this web-site is transmitted directly to our merchant bank and never stored locally on our servers. Nobody at Zuzutop outside of those needed to process your product request has access to your financial information.

You may, from time to time, receive information from us regarding new features, new products and special offers we think you’ll find valuable. If you’d like to opt out of receiving future mailings from Zuzutop.com, please click on the “Contact Us” tab and send us a message with the subject line “Remove Me.”

Zuzutop.com also may use your personal information to pre- forms that are used by the Site to facilitate transactions with us and save you from entering every data field on the checkout.

## Service Providers

We work with third parties who provide many administrative services. These services include order processing and fulfillment, e commerce connections, credit card clearance, website hosting, data compilation and email related services. Personally identifiable information, including financial information, is shared with such third parties for the purpose of providing such services and is limited to the intended purpose only.

We do not disclose a customer’s personal information to third parties for any third-party direct marketing purposes. If you have been contacted by a third party, other than Zuzutop or one of its subsidiaries, who is privy to information you provided us, please contact our customer service department immediately and we will do everything in our power to investigate your problem.

In addition, we also allow you to decide whether you want to receive further marketing information from us. If you do not want Zuzutop.com to send you announcements or special offers by email, please click on the “Contact Us” tab and send us a message with the subject line “Remove Me.”

Subject to the applicable law, we reserve the right to release information concerning any Site visitor where such visitor is believed to be in violation of his or her obligations to us, is partaking (or is suspected of partaking) in any illegal activity, in response to civil subpoenas and discovery requests, to protect the interests of Zuzutop.com, our customers or others, and as otherwise permitted or required by law.

Emails from Zuzutop.com or its business partners, and the Site itself, may contain links to other Internet websites, including sites that may or may not be owned or operated by Zuzutop.com. Unless otherwise explicitly stated, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites, including such sites’ use of any information (such as IP number, browser type or operating system) collected when email recipients or Site visitors click through links to those sites. If you visit such websites, we encourage you to become familiar with the privacy practices of the sites to ensure a safe browsing experience.

Zuzutop.com seeks to use reasonable security measures to help protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of personally identifiable information that is under our control. Unfortunately, no security system, or system of transmitting data over the Internet, can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result of the foregoing, while we seek to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee server security, the means by which information is transmitted between you and us, or any information provided to us or to any third party through or in connection with the Site. You provide all such information at your own risk.

## A Special Note About Children’s Privacy

You must be at least 18 years old to have our permission to use this Site. We do not knowingly collect, use or disclose Personal Information about visitors under 18 years of age. If you are a minor, you can use this service only in conjunction with your parent’s or guardian’s permission.

## Governing Law

This Privacy Policy forms part of our Website Terms of Use and as such shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Florida in the United States of America without regard to conflicts of a law principles. You hereby consent and waive all objection to jurisdiction of the federal and state courts of the state Florida and to venue therein.

## My Account

If you have signed up with Zuzutop.com, you may update your mailing address, email address, name changes or telephone number on the Contact Us page. If you have any questions about the Policy or if you wish to report any violations of the Policy, you can mail us at: info@zuzutop.com

## Customer Service

Member RX 1201 Orange St, Suite 600 Wilmington, Newcastle, DE 19801 or by visting Zuzutop.com

## Contact Us

Zuzutop.com is committed to the best customer service. We constantly review customer feedback to improve and enhance the online shopping experience. You can provide immediate feedback by sending us an email at info@zuzutop.com.
